export const questionsAndAnswers = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: '23 x 76',
    options: [1111, 1748, 2322, 988],
    answer: 1748,
    questionType: 'math',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: '11 x 22',
    options: [242, 121, 111, 123],
    answer: 242,
    questionType: 'math',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: '434 x 23',
    options: [9982, 9984, 9989, 9992],
    answer: 9982,
    questionType: 'math',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: '53 x 24',
    options: [1172, 1227, 1272, 1232],
    answer: 1272,
    questionType: 'math',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: '24 x 22',
    options: [508, 518, 528, 548],
    answer: 528,
    questionType: 'math',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: '34 x 23',
    options: [782, 788, 792, 796],
    answer: 782,
    questionType: 'math',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: '46 x 32',
    options: [1442, 1462, 1472, 1476],
    answer: 1472,
    questionType: 'math',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: '65 x 24',
    options: [1260, 1460, 1560, 1660],
    answer: 1560,
    questionType: 'math',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: '57 x 38',
    options: [2066, 2166, 2266, 2466],
    answer: 2166,
    questionType: 'math',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: '54 x 32',
    options: [1728, 1729, 1738, 1768],
    answer: 1728,
    questionType: 'math',
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: '13 x 11',
    options: [111, 123, 133, 143],
    answer: 143,
    questionType: 'math',
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: '77 x 43',
    options: [3112, 3312, 1233, 1234],
    answer: 3312,
    questionType: 'math',
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: 'Select Color: ',
    key: 'YELLOW',
    options: ['GREEN', 'RED', 'BLUE', 'YELLOW', 'BLACK'],
    answer: 'RED',
    questionType: 'stroop',
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: 'Select Color: ',
    key: 'BROWN',
    options: ['GREEN', 'RED', 'BLUE', 'YELLOW', 'BLACK'],
    answer: 'RED',
    questionType: 'stroop',
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: 'Select Color: ',
    key: 'GREEN',
    options: ['GREEN', 'RED', 'BLUE', 'YELLOW', 'BLACK'],
    answer: 'BLUE',
    questionType: 'stroop',
  },
  //   {
  //     id: 16,
  //     question: '',
  //     options: [],
  //     answer: '',
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 17,
  //     question: '',
  //     options: [],
  //     answer: '',
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 18,
  //     question: '',
  //     options: [],
  //     answer: '',
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 19,
  //     question: '',
  //     options: [],
  //     answer: '',
  //   },
  //   {
  //     id: 20,
  //     question: '',
  //     options: [],
  //     answer: '',
  //   },
];

export const getLength = () => {
  return 15;
};
